那么我们为什么要添加类型呢？
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So
why would we wanna add types?
为什么有人要做这个项目呢？
Why would someone bother
to make this project?
首先，它让我们有机会进行假设
First, it gives us the opportunity
to take assumptions and
当我们编写一段代码时，我们作为作者所受到的约束。
constraints we have as authors
when we write a piece of code.
它给了我们一个机会，使这些成为我们的代码的一部分。
It gives us an opportunity to
make those a part of our code.
所以如果你有一个设计用字符串作为参数的函数,
So if you have a function that's designed
to take a string as an argument,
你有一个地方可以说，这个参数必须是一个字符串。
you actually have a place where you could
say, this argument must be a string.
现在，如果我们只看普通的 JavaScript,
Now, if we were just looking
at regular JavaScript,
你可以写一个注释说，请只传递字符串给这个函数。
you could write a comment saying,
please only pass string to this function.
但是你需要依靠人们阅读你的源代码并找到它。
But you'd be relying on people reading
your source code and finding that.
你可以断言它是一个类似函数中的字符串，抛出
You could assert that it's a string
like within the function, throwing
如果这个值的类型不是一个字符串，但是这个值开始增加，那么就会出现一个错误。
error if the type of this value is not
a string, but that starts to add up.
它开始朝着我们称之为防御性编程的方向发展。
It starts to get towards something
we would call defensive programming.
这就是你基本上不相信你的任何投入和
Which is where you basically don't
trust any of your inputs and
它带来了大量的开销和复杂性,
it introduces a lot of overhead and
complexity,
性能开销和认知开销，对吗？
both performance overhead and
cognitive overhead, right?
你雇了一个新人加入你的团队，他们必须迂回前进
You hire a new person to your team and
they're gonna have to weave through
然后找出这些论断的出处
the stuff and
figure out where are the assertions and
这个函数在确认数据正确后的实际作用是什么。
what's this function actually doing after
it's satisfied that the data is correct.
这使得事情有点难以维持。
It makes things a little
difficult to maintain.
所以这些类型帮助我们获得所有的开发人员
So this types assist us in
taking all of our developer
并将其编码到我们编写的代码中。
intent and
encoding it into the code we write.
类型帮助我们发现常见的错误，比如拼写错误。
Types help us catch common mistakes,
like a spelling error.
我每天都会犯几次拼写错误，至少在第二次或者第三次之前
I make spelling errors a few times a day,
at least leading up to my second or
第三杯咖啡，拼写错误是很常见的。
third cup of coffee,
spelling errors are very common.
因为有一个验证，你只访问属性
So because there's a validation that
you're only accessing the properties
你应该访问，你正确命名你的参数。
that you should be accessing and that
you're naming your arguments correctly.
因为你已经定义了类型，所以你不太可能使用这些类型
You're less likely to make those
with types because you've defined
什么东西应该被访问，还有其他你不应该碰的东西。
what should be accessed, and everything
else you should not be trying to touch.
一个不完整的重构和其他好例子。
An incomplete refactors and
other good example.
假设你在四个地方使用一个函数
Imagine you have a function that
you're using in four places and
你再加上一个必要的论点
you add another required argument and
你只更新了三个电话网站，其中一个过期了。
you only update three of the call
sites leaving one out of date.
编译器会让您知道这里存在不匹配，因此
The compiler will let you know
that there is a mismatch here, so
它有助于捕捉那些在 JavaScript 中很难捕捉到的东西。
it helps catch that kind of thing which
is very difficult to catch in JavaScript.
你会看到我们今天的工作，我们正在移动我们会发现的许多错误
You'll see throughout our work today that
we're moving a lot of errors we would find
在运行时直到编译时。
at run time up to compile time.
所以我们得到了更早的反馈
So we're getting earlier feedback and
我们从静态分析中得到了反馈。
we're getting feedback as
a result of static analysis.
这是一个分析，只是看看你的源代码，并得出结论。
Which is an analysis that just looks at
your source code and comes to conclusions.
与运行时分析相反，运行时分析需要你实际经历和
As opposed to runtime analysis which
requires you to actually go through and
执行代码的每一条路径。
execute every path of your code.
所以你可以通过测试捕捉到一些东西，绝对的。
So you could catch some of
the stuff with tests, absolutely.
但是当你写代码的时候
But while you're writing your code and
也许你还没有完成你的考试，也许你的考试不完整,
maybe you haven't written your test yet,
or maybe your test are incomplete,
这里有人在做一个测试不完美的项目吗？
is anyone here worked on a project
that has an imperfect test suite?
我已经，所有的人现在都应该上去了。
I have, all hands should go up right now.
你们所有的测试服可能都不完美。
All of your test suits
are probably imperfect.
因此，这意味着您不需要依靠测试来捕捉这种类型的错误。
So, this means you are not depending
on tests to catch this type of error.
您当然可以犯其他类型的错误。
You certainly can make
other types of errors.
最后，你马上就会看到打字稿是基础
And then finally right away, you're gonna
see that TypeScript is the foundation
一个伟大的开发经验。
of a great developer experience.
这是 JavaScript 生态系统一直缺失的东西
It's something that the JavaScript
ecosystem has kind of been missing
相对的两种类型程序设计语言。
relative two typed programming languages.
所以我从一个 Java 开发者开始
So I started out as a Java developer and
我使用了各种各样的 ide 来编写代码。
I used a wide-range of
IDEs to write my code in.
我有很多大纲，告诉我这些是课程
And I've got a lot of outlines
showing me these are the classes and
这些是班级的成员，这些是公开的，这些是私人的。
these are the members of the classes, and
these are public and these are private.
我得到了很好的自动完成，因为语言是这样设置的
And I got great auto-completes because
the language was setup in such a way
你可以知道你应该访问什么，不该访问什么。
that you could know what you're supposed
to be accessing and what you're not.
你访问的东西的价值是什么？
And what is the value of
the thing you are accessing?
这在像 JavaScript 这样的动态类型语言中是很难理解的
This is much harder to figure out in a
dynamically typed language like JavaScript
或者 Ruby。
or Ruby.